jazp.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

 **Is shopping on Jazp.com secure?**

Absolutely. Our site uses the latest SSL encryption technology, which ensures that all data, including your personal information, remains private and secure.

We also use CyberSource, a secure global payment management platform, so you can use your credit card to shop at Jazp.com, completely stress-free.

Our Privacy Policy also explains everything else we do to keep your personal information secure, once received. Once you place an order the seller confirms receipt of the order and begins processing it.

Jazp.com gives a complete guarantee for the protection of privacy of site visitors and customers. Since we understand the importance of the privacy of each person, we place high value on a customer’s privacy. We never share customer information with any third parties except to deliver a service to you, for instance arranging product delivery, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of customer research and profiling, or where we have your express permission to do so. We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party without your permission. However we cannot be responsible or held liable for the actions of third party sites from which you may have linked or been directed to the Jazp.com website.  

**Communication & Marketing** If you have registered on our site with and/or made a purchase from Jazp.com we, and selected third parties, may occasionally update you on our latest products, news and special offers via e-mail, post & telephone. As a member, you are able to opt-out of receiving such communication any time by unsubscribing to our email newsletters when received. You are able to do this by clicking on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email newsletter you have received from us, or by contacting us through the [Contact Us](http://www.jazp.com/www.jazp.com/contactus) section of the site.

**Data that we collect**

We will use the information you provide to enable us to process your orders and to provide you with the services and information offered through our website and which you request.

Further, we will use the information you provide to administer your account with us; verify and carry out financial transactions in relation to payments you make online; audit the downloading of data from our website; improve the layout and/or content of the pages of our website and customise them for users; identify visitors on our website; carry out research on our users’ demographics; send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us, including information about our products and services, provided you have indicated that you have not objected to being contacted for these purposes. Subject to obtaining your consent we may contact you by email with details of other products and services. If you prefer not to receive any marketing communications from us, you can opt out at any time. We may pass your name and address on to a third party in order to make delivery of the product to you for e.g.: to couriers or suppliers. Your phone number may be used for notifications regarding order status and announcements of latest deals and campaigns. Payments that you make through the Site will be processed by our agent. The information you provide to us must be accurate and not deceiving and you are requested to update your account and personal information when it necessary.  You may check your order details by logging into your account on the site

**Site Statistics**

We may disclose aggregate, anonymised statistics about the number of visitors to this Website or number of purchases made as required by our investors. We use an independent measurement and research company to gather data regarding the visitors to this Website on our behalf using cookies and a code which is embedded in the site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information. Jazp.com uses and stores this type of information, as with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help it improve the services to its users. Further information regarding the way in which this information is obtained and used can be obtained by contacting us through the [Contact US](http://www.jazp.com/contactus) section of the site _._

**Protecting your security**

We may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your identity - a credit check is not performed and your credit rating is unaffected.

**Transfers of your Information** The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the UAE. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the UAE who work for Jazp.com or one of our suppliers or agencies. Such processing may, for example, be required in order to fulfill your order, process your payment details or provide support services. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal data, but cannot guarantee the security of data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

**Disclosure of personal information**  We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

                            If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Jazp.com, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Third party sites   **

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Checking your Details**

If you wish to verify the details you have submitted to Jazp.com you may do so by contacting us via the Contact Us section. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information. This proof of identity will take the form of your e-mail address and password submitted upon registration. You must therefore keep this information safe as you will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information.

**Unsubscribing from Newsletter**

  1.  You can unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time. Since we want you to stay up to date with our fantastic offers, we suggest you keep your       newsletter subscription active.
  2.  If you do wish to unsubscribe, the easiest way to do this is to click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any newsletter you receive from us, or  send an email to [unsubscribe@jazp.com](mailto:unsubscribemail@jazp.com) 
  3.   You may also contact us via the methods listed in the [Contact Us](http://www.jazp.com/contactus) section of the site.

**Amendments to Terms & Conditions**The website Policies and Terms & Conditions may be changed or updated occasionally to meet requirements and standards. Therefore, customers are encouraged to frequently visit these sections in order to be updated on the website. Modifications will be effective from the day they are posted on the website.
